# Cristobal Colmenares

## Software developer / Full Stack web developer

⊕ Venezuela



## **Skills**



### **About me**

Software Developer focused on building products with special attention to details, Technology enthusiast, with skills in different backend and frontend web environment development environments as well as mobile development. Experience with administrative systems, biometric devices, facial recognition, and everything that corresponds to software development.

## Work experience

LatamEarth 2023 - Present

Full Stack developer

System integrates multiple libraries with React.js and Next.js uses to improve productivity and code quality. It handles user registration forms, manages files and databases for administrative purposes, and displays data in tables. It also manages various APIs, has error handling, and provides scalable and understandable code. UX design improves user interaction with the system.

Stack: TypeScript React.js Zustand Next.js Tailwind CSS Node.js Supabase PostgreSQL Prisma Railway Git

OgrosGameShop 2022 - 2023

#### Frontend developer

Website style design taking into account UI/UX to facilitate the user's navigation through e-commerce, integration of administrative panel for the management of products through a CMS, management and integration of social networks for customer service

Stack: PHP JQuery WordPress MySql Shopify

### Freelance & Proyecto personales

2021 - Present

Full Stack developer

Build an e-commerce website, Profile, Creation of Web application, Handle extracted data, Third-party integrations.

Stack: Redux Supabase AWS JavaScript TypeScript React.js Next.js Node.js

Express.js Nest.js

### **Jupiter Suministros C.A**

2022 - 2020

Web Administrator & Technical Maintenance

Updating and Maintenance of computer equipment both in Hardware and Software, keeping them updated for the productivity of the employees and the company, thus avoiding inconsistency.

Stack: JavaScript PHP MySql

**Education** 

Language

Universidad de Oriente 2017 - 2021

Civil engineering

Spanish - Native English - B1